Isn't it cold?
寒くない?
The wind is strong.
風が強い
But her feet are very beautiful.
でも足がとても綺麗だな
Have you lost weight?
痩せた?
I feel like I'm getting thinner.
なんか細くなった気がする
Are you eating rice?
ご飯食べてる?
I ate it, but it was too cold and I wanted to drink something warm.
食べたんですけど寒すぎて温かいの飲みたいな
Then let's go to the family room.
じゃあ家庭部屋行こうか
Today, it looks like a stuffed rabbit.
今日もウサギのぬいぐるみみたいな感じになってる
Is this part new?
このパーツ新しく?
I had it for a while, but I decided to try it on.
前から持ってたんですけど、着てみました
I also have an image of wearing fluffy white.
白もふわふわで着てるイメージ
It feels like winter.
冬っぽい
This clothes.
この服
Shall I buy it so you can come to me again?
今度も俺のところに来るように買おうか
Would you like to do so?
ぜひ、いいんですか?
What kind of clothes do you like?
なんか好きな服は?
It might be quite different.
結構バラバラかも
Should I buy clothes that I think are cute?
可愛いって思った服を買おうか
I saw what I could get and decided on that name.
取れそうを見て、その名前だと
See if you can get it.
取れそうを見て
Do you see clothes that look like your height?
身長みたいな服見えてる?
It can be served.
盛れる
About 13 cm.
13センチくらいの
Hot caramel is also available at Thor.
ホットのキャラメルだって、トールで
The way you're holding it is really cute.
なんか持ち方めっちゃ可愛いね
With both hands.
両手で
It's completely warm now.
完全にもう温まる
It's dangerous, all of a sudden.
やばいですね、急に
It's warm.
温まりました
Is school already over winter vacation?
学校ってもう冬休み終わった?
It's winter vacation now.
今、冬休みです
Is it still winter vacation?
まだ冬休み?
It's quite long.
結構長いね
That's nice.
いいなぁ
copper?
どう?
Have you noticed anything recently?
最近何かパッパッとする?
Are you doing anything other than apps?
アプリ以外でも何かやってるの?
Now it's a dating club in Roppongi.
今は六本木の交際クラブ
Are you going there?
そんなとこ行ってんの?
Customer service member?
客層員?
There are a lot of nice people there.
結構いい人が多いです
Make time for me.
ちゃんと俺の時間作って
He's kind of smiling, but he doesn't say much.
なんかニコニコしてるけど、あんまり喋んないあたり
why?
なんで?
He's so smart, it seems like he's doing a lot of calculations.
あざといから、色々なんかすげー計算してそう
Today it's pink.
今日はピンク
copper
どう
What do you mean?
な ってんの?
We're separated.
別れてる
This one is erotic, somehow.
これ一枚エロいね、なんか
I want to let you wear whatever I want for my hobby.
俺の趣味で着せたいもの着せたい
Where do you usually buy it?
いつもどこで買う?
Like Lumine?
ルミネとか?
There are a lot of Lumine.
ルミネ多いですね
Not yet.
まだダメ
what?
何?
why?
なんで?
Why is that okay?
なんでいいじゃん
It's already getting bigger.
もう大きくなってる
It's happening.
なってるよ
When we were walking together earlier, he was standing the whole time.
さっき一緒に歩いてる時はずっと立ってるよ
I'll give you my mouth first.
先に口でしてあげるよ
first.
最 初
what?
何?
I'll do it with my mouth.
口でしてあげる
Seriously?
マジで?
Yeah.
うん
After that, go to this place.
その後もこのとこ行ってよ
I've been eating it for two weeks.
2週間食べてきた
this.
これ
I'll take it off.
外しちゃう
Yeah.
うん
My hair on your butt and face
お尻に顔に僕の毛が
be.
ある
No, I'll go buy some.
いや、 俺買いに行く
Ah, I think I'm going.
あー、行きそう
Ah, let's go.
あー、行く
I'm going to buy something.
買いに行く
Yeah.
うん
Why didn't you stop and leave?
なぜだって止まり去らなかったんだって
Yeah yeah.
うんうん
It was really stopped.
めっちゃ止まってたんだって
Do you understand?
分かる?
You know, yourself.
知ってるでしょ、自分で
The moment I was released from being on the verge of death, I felt like I was moving so much.
死にかけんのから解放されて瞬間にめっちゃ動いてるねって
This is what I wrote.
書いたのこんなの
It's very colorful though.
めっちゃ色いんだけど
I hadn't taken any pictures until now.
ここまで撮ってなかった
This too?
これも?
Are you going to take this too?
これも撮るの?
Yeah.
うん
Are you going to take this too?
これも撮るの?
Please take a picture.
撮ってみてね
It might be a good idea to take pictures while being a little nervous.
ちょっとしこりながら撮るといいかもし
Not possible.
れない
Your waist is soft.
腰 柔らかいよね
Is your waist soft?
腰柔らかい?
He's really cute, the way the people in the background look at me.
なんかね、バックの人とかのこっち見る仕草とかめっちゃ可愛い子
It was.
だ った
Eh heh.
え へへ
I washed this place properly without crying.
泣くなししたらここ洗った、ちゃんと
Drink it if you can.
出来たら飲んでよ
picture?
え?
Drink if you can, kid.
出来たら飲んでよ、この子は
Eh heh.
え へへ
Somehow, a girl got crazy and did something like this.
なんか女の子がガイマタになってこうやってやっちゃって
Like this.
こうやって
I can't even see the bathroom.
風呂も絶対見えないけど
I did it beautifully.
綺麗にやっちゃった
Ehehe.
えへへ
Are you okay now?
もう大丈夫?
Yeah.
うん
Enough is enough, right?
もういいでしょう?
Yeah, it's okay.
うん、大丈夫
Ehehe.
えへへ